https://cadroncreek.com/policies/

Policies - Cadron Creek
Skip to contentOrders over $50 receive Free Shipping! *USA
Search for:
Main Menu
HomeShopClearancePoliciesMenu TogglePrivacy PolicySupport PolicyReturn PolicyOrdering InformationMenu ToggleBack OrdersGroup & Co-op OrdersInternational OrdersOrder FulfillmentOrder OptionsContactMy Account
Cart / $0.00
0
PoliciesPrivacy PolicyThe Cadron Creek Christian Curriculum Internet Privacy Policy governs how we treat personal information collected through our web sites and Internet servers. “Personal and business information” is any information we receive from you that identifies you individually, including your name, your address, email address, phone number and other information you supply and that is not otherwise publicly available.The information we gather is not shared, sold or exchanged with any other agency or business. We treat your information with the same degree of confidentiality we use with our own information. You may request that Cadron Creek Christian Curriculum remove your information at any time by contacting us via email: Cadron Creek Christian Curriculum.Cadron Creek Christian Curriculum may collect personal information when you purchase products, register with us for email updates or request other information requiring personal identification. Cadron Creek Christian Curriculum may collect information about your use of this web site to better serve you in the future, including information about your use of the products and online resources we offer. Cadron Creek Christian Curriculum tracks and stores information we receive from your Internet browser, including your IP address and the pages you visit.Cadron Creek Christian Curriculum uses this information to tailor the design and appearance of our web site, to improve the offerings we provide, and to better serve the customers and visitors of the Cadron Creek Christian Curriculum web site.Support PolicyWe’re always available to help you use Cadron Creek’s homeschooling resources. Please feel free to write, email or call during business hours:marigold@cadroncreek.comCadron Creek Christian Curriculum4329 Pinos Altos RoadSilver City, NM 88061-7891 USA(505) 534-1496Return PolicyAll items purchased from us may be returned within 30 days. Full credit, excluding shipping charges, will be given provided the materials are returned in a resalable condition.Our ApproachPioneer EraNarnian EraVictorian EraSample FilesCompanionsAbout Margie GrayAsk MargieLinksOn-line Discussion Groups
Cadron Creek 4329 Hwy 15 Silver City, NM 88061 United States Tel : 575-534-1496 Email : marigold@cadroncreek.com Copyright © 2020 Cadron Creek
Scroll to Top
